

Game Developer with a strong passion for Music for Videogames. Worked at Bliss Games as Unity Game Programmer developing mobile games for Android/iOS.

Studied a Videogames Development Bachelor's Degree at ENTI-UB Barcelona. Creator of immersive music soundtracks for games like CONCRETE using FMOD.

#### **Axel Castells Monllau** Game Developer and Programmer



(+34) 623 10 34 34



M axelcastellsmonllau@gmail.com

## **Technical Skills**

**Unreal Engine Development** (Blueprints) Unity Programming (C#) JavaScript C / C++ **SQL** Databases

## Non-tehnical Skills

Good at teamworking Communicative Creative problem solver Learn with agility

## **Engines and Tools**

**Unreal Engine 4** Unity Wwise / FMOD Cubase / Logic Pro X Autodesk 3D Max Blender

## Languages

**English** Advanced Spanish Native Catalan Native



axelcastells.github.io



linkedin.com/in/axelcastells

# Experience

**Game Programmer** Bliss Games

2020 - Now

Fast prototyping and developing hyper-casual games for Android and iOS platforms.

Deep learning on monetisation and IAP solutions for mobile games.

Extensive use of SQL databases to save / read game

Blockchain games, using SDKs such as Stardust and Venly.

**Game Programmer** *Labs4Reality* 

2018 - 2019

Developing AR (Augmented Reality) applications. Cohesive teamwork using agile methodologies.

**Intern Programmer** Pupgam Studios

Working on UI programming and design on a small team using Scrum.

#### Education

**University Degree in Game Development** 2015 - 2020 (Barcelona, Spain) **ENTI-UB** 

**HND** in Creative Media Production 2013 - 2015 (Barcelona, Spain) CEV-Barcelona

## Interests

As someone who has grown up in a family of musicians I've always been surrounded by music, which pushed me to develop a strong passion for it in my adulthood. I also enjoy reading, roleplaying games, martial arts and studying languages.

Some other frameworks, libraries, languages or tools I've used in the past: SQL, SDL, SFML, OpenGL, Arduino, Processing, Reaper...